Finding Aid for Edwin Whitney Bishop sermons, 1909-1935
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Edwin Whitney Bishop sermons
1909-1935
Bishop, Edwin Whitney, 1869-
[751] DA 2; B622; S486
24 items 1 box
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The provenance of the sermons is unknown.
No further additions to the collection are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Edwin Whitney Bishop was a Congregational clergyman. He had pastorates in several communities, including Grand Rapids and Lansing, Michigan.
This is an accumulation of the sermons of Edwin Whitney Bishop, gathered together from different sources.
The Edwin Whitney Bishop sermons consists of 24 sermons delivered between 1909 and 1935.
Subjects:
Sermons--American.
- Sermons, 1909-1935
  - What is it to be a Christian Minister?., 1909 (Box 1)
  - Some Spiritual Perils of the Business Life., February 1911 (Box 1)
  - Jesus Christ, Pioneer in Personality., March 1911 (Box 1)
  - Jesus Christ, Gentleman., April 1911 (Box 1)
  - Mother and Grandmother., May 1911 (Box 1)
  - Seventy-five Years Ago., October 1911 (Box 1)
  - Micah vs. Mars., December 1911 (Box 1)
  - (Christmas Sermon), 1911 (Box 1)
  - Some Permanent Lessons from the Loss of the Titanic., April 1912 (Box 1)
  - The Basis of Government., November 1912 (Box 1)
  - What Shall we Say about the Floods?, April 1913 (Box 1)
  - Our Country for All., November 1913 (Box 1)
  - Park Church White Papers., 1914 (Box 1)
  - Seventy-Five Years Ago, 1911., 1922 (Box 1)
  - Christ and Coue., January 1923 (Box 1)
  - His Last Day., March 1923 (Box 1)
  - Can One Believe in Evolution and be a Christian?, October 1923 (Box 1)
  - What is the Matter With the Youth of Today?, 1924 (Box 1)
  - Boys and Christ., 1925 (Box 1)
  - Let Us Understand., 1926 (Box 1)
  - Can It Come?, 1927 (Box 1)
  - Our Next-Door Neighbor., 1928 (Box 1)
  - The Return of Symbolism., 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Church of the Pilgrims, 1935 (Box 1)